

ABOUT:

A young professional who is well skilled and detail oriented in the computing/tech field. Being involved with computers and electronics for over 20 years, having learned skills from replacing/repairing hardware (desktop computers, laptops, smartphones) to installing operating systems (WIN/MAC), and writing code (HTML/CSS, JAVASCRIPT, React, Node.js). Along with troubleshooting modern systematical errors. Problem solving abilities come with ease. An opportunist to provide skills towards a well suited role.

CONTACT:

PHONE: 317-789-5478

E-MAIL: insighteuphoric@gmail.com

WEBSITE:

https://u4ik.github.io/

Hobbies

Audio Production Video Production Media Design Writing Code Writing Music

AMIT S. MANGAT

WEB DEVELOPER/CREATIVE DESIGNER

EDUCATION

[International Academy of Design & Technology]

02/2011 - 03/2012

[Learned basic computer skills, hardware and software.] [4.0 GPA – Placed on President's List]

[Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis]

07/2011 - 06/2012

[Beginner SQL, & HTML/CSS, advanced computing techniques] [3.5GPA – Placed on Dean's List]

[Eleven Fifty Academy]

02/2020 -08/2020]

[Advanced JavaScript, advanced React & Node.js, advanced HTML/CSS, advanced skills working with Git and Heroku. Advanced experience working with node, building full stack PERN web apps.]

WORK EXPERIENCE

[Best Buy] - [Computer Sales]

06/2016 - 12/2018

[Earned top gun, being the highest sales associate within the district. Provided support and solutions about electronics to everyday personal and professional consumers. Consistent with the completion of target goals assigned daily and monthly.]

Reference: Nate Bandy (General Manager, Best Buy)

Contact: 317-201-413

[Premium Retail - Oculus] – [Facebook Brand Ambassador]

06/2018 - 02/2020

[Team lead for my territory to build the displays for the Oculus Quest] [Being a brand Ambassador for Facebook, I provided updates and troubleshooting of their devices located in retail stores. As well as promoting their devices, being a face of the company.

Reference: Heather Ingo (PremiumRetail Northeast Division Manager)

Contact: (630)-774-2240

CURRENT

[Eleven Fifty Academy] – [JavaScript Web Dev. Learning Assistant] 08/2020 – Current

[Excelling at my role as a learning assistant. Providing students with the understandings of modern-day web development. Providing help through debugging, answering questions, providing resources, guidance towards success within each cohort.]

Reference: Mary Dougherty (Director of Learning)

Contact: (317)-421-7961